Stanislav Khramtsov

Professional Summary

I am Frontend Developer with more than 3 years of experience in React and Django development.

I developed an electronic document management system for my last workplace. In time I added HR and counterparties databases to this site and turned system into CRM. This system is constantly used by about 100 employees.

In 2022 I created scheduler webpage for a dental office without using third-party schedule libraries.

I have experience in developing static sites on HTML5+CSS3, Pug. I am learning new CSS features and plan to add SASS to my stack.

I read about Agile methodologies and would not mind joining an agile team.

In the future, I see myself as a Fullstack JS Developer. Next step for me is learning Next.js. I also plan to learn TypeScript.

Job Goal

Junior Frontend Developer.

Technical Skills

- React
- **JavaScript**
- HTML5
- CSS3

- Django
- Bootstrap 4
- Pug
- Webpack

Experience

System administrator

Perechin Timber and Chemical Plant

2015 - 2022

- Development and support of electronic document management system (Django + React)
- Development of kk.com.ua web-page (Pug + Bootstrap 4).
- Installation and repair of computer equipment and software. Technical support to employees, solving software problems.

Finance department specialist (2014-2015), Citizen appeals department specialist (2013-2014)

Perechyn district state administration

2013-2015

- Processing of district budgets.
- Processing of citizens appeals, support of the website of the district state administration, writing and publishing articles about the employer.

Print designer

Newspaper «Narodne slovo»

2009 - 2013

- Design and layout of weekly newspaper.
- Work in Adobe InDesign and Adobe Photoshop.

Email: khramtsov.react@gmail.com Phone: 095 55 329 77

Github: https://github.com/sauron4er Portfolio: https://sauron4er.github.io/resume/

LinkedIn: <u>Перейти</u>

Telegram: Stanislav Khramtsov

Frontend Developer

System administrator

Computer club Svit Online

2008 - 2009

Customer service, typing, searching for information on the Internet.

Education

2003 - 2008: Bachelor's degree in Banking, Uzhgorod National University.

Certificates:

English | React | HTML & CSS | Web Developer | Digital education (Diia)

Languages

- Ukrainian Native;
- English C2 Proficient (I read books without a dictionary, watch TV shows without subtitles, but for now I lack reallife communication experience);
- Russian Advanced;

More Info

- I love to study. I learned programming while working on real projects.
- I maintain friendly relations with colleagues. I like to help and am not shy to ask for advice.
- Years of freelance work parallel to the main job made me stress-resistant. Currently, I am no longer engaged in freelancing.
- Extensive experience in InDesign has taught me to pay attention to small details.
- I spend my free time with my beloved wife and daughter. I like to read books, play FPL.

Email: <u>khramtsov.react@gmail.com</u>
Phone: 095 55 329 77

Github: https://github.com/sauron4er
Portfolio: https://sauron4er.github.io/resume/

LinkedIn: <u>Перейти</u>

Telegram: <u>Stanislav Khramtsov</u>